Contact

sferadev@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sferadev (LinkedIn) www.github.com/SferaDev (Portfolio)

Top Skills

JavaScript Node.js Git

Alexis Rico

Software Engineer at EyeSeeTea LTD

Barcelona Area, Spain

Summary

Designing code for both the private sector and open source initiatives.

Work experience as a developer on Node.js backend servers, frontend ReactJS web applications, Mobile app development for Android and maintainer of complex distributed code repositories.

Currently building applications for large scale deployments of District Health Information System 2 (DHIS2).

Languages and technologies: Javascript, Java, Kotlin, Android SDK, C++, Git, Gerrit, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Alexa Skills Kit...

Experience

EyeSeeTea LTD Software Engineer February 2019 - Present

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya Intern Software Engineer February 2018 - Present

Paranoid Android - AOSPA AOSP Developer November 2013 - October 2017 (4 years)

Education

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya Bachelor's degree, Software Engineering · (2015 - 2019)